Guide to the University of Chicago Department of History Records 1905-1990
University of Chicago Library
- Series IV: Restricted
  - Subseries 2: Academic Restrictions
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Joranson, E., Folder 2, 1938-1948 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Jordan-Knappen, 1930-1943 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Koht-Lach, 1943-1957 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Larsen, J.A.O., Folder 1, 1931-1941 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Larsen, J.A.O., Folder 2, 1941-1955 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Lavengood-McLaughlin, 1927-1957 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, MacNair, H.F., Folder 1, 1928-1937 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, MacNair, H.F., Folder 2, 1937-1947 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, McNeill, J.T., 1935-1944 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, McNeill-Miller, 1926-1957 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Mommsen-Mowat, 1950-1957 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Nef-Nicholson, 1935-1956 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Olmstead-Pauck, 1930-1955 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Pierce, B., Folder 1, 1930-1938 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Pierce, B., Folder 2, 1938-1953 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Porges-Quigley, 1932-1957 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Riker-Rippy, 1920-1956 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Roebuck-Rothfels, 1946-1956 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Rotter-Schmitt, 1924-1952 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Schmitt, B.E., 1935-1944 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Scott, 1930-1949 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Simpson-Sweet, 1941-1957 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Tawney-[Staff], 1930-1957 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - History, Faculty Personnel Cards, 1931-1953 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - History, Examination Reports, MA, PhD, Folder 1, 1949-1954 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - History, Examination Reports, MA, PhD, Folder 2, 1955-1956 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - History, Examination Reports, MA, PhD, Folder 3, 1956-1957 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - History, Correspondence and Reports, Placements, Folder 1, 1958-1959 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - History, Correspondence and Reports, Placements, Folder 2, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - History, Correspondence and Reports, Placements, Folder 3, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - History, Correspondence and Reports, Placements, Folder 4, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - History, Correspondence and Reports, Placements, Folder 5, 1961-1962 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - History, Correspondence and Reports, Placements, Folder 6, 1962-1964 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - History, Courses, Hutchinson, Folder 1, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - History, Courses, Hutchinson, Folder 2, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - History, Courses, Boorstin, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - History, Comprehensive Examinations, Records, Folder 1, 1932-1956 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - History, Comprehensive Examinations, Records, Folder 2, 1933-1946 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - History, B.A. Students, Records Cards, Folder 3, 1939-1956 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - History, Fellowships, Folder 1, 1961-1972 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - History, Fellowships, Folder 2, 1968-1972 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - History, Fellowships, Folder 3, 1968-1972 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - History, Fellowships, Folder 4, 1971-1975 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - History, Fellowships, Folder 5, 1973-1975 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - History, Fellowships, Folder 6, 1973-1975 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - History, MA, Divisional Program, Recommendations, 1970-1979 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - History, Attrition Data, 1968-1976 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - History, American Field Committee, Applicants, 1971-1984 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - History, Department, Chairman’s Report, Folder 1, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - History, Department, Chairman’s Report, Folder 2, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - History, Lurcy Fellowship, Student Applications, Folder 1, 1973-1975 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - History, Lurcy Fellowship, Student Applications, Folder 2, 1973-1975 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - History, Lurcy Fellowship, Student Applications, Folder 3, 1974-1976 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - History, Lurcy Fellowship, Student Applications, Folder 4, 1974-1975 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - History, Lurcy Fellowship, Student Applications, Folder 5, 1974-1975 (Box 58, Folder 9)